upclick.com 2008-06-22

# UpClick Privacy Policy

Online privacy is constantly evolving and UpClick.com plans to take all reasonable efforts to maintain up to date and effective online privacy standards and practices. We have linked every page of our website ("Website") to this page for your convenience and you may also contact us with any questions or concerns that you may have.

UpClick.com is committed to respecting your online privacy and recognizes your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us. In order to provide our services, UpClick.com collects and uses your Personal Information provided during your purchase. Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home, a credit card information, and Website passwords. This policy explains how we intend to treat your Personal Information.   
If you choose to provide us with your Personal Information on our Website, we may transfer that Information within UpClick.com or to UpClick.com 's third-party service providers, across borders, and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. 

UpClick.com strives to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy. Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, UpClick.com intends to adhere to the principles set forth in this Privacy Policy even if, in connection with the above, we transfer your Personal Information from your country to countries that may not require an "adequate" level of protection for your Personal Information. In other words, our goal is to provide protection for your Personal Information no matter where that Personal Information is collected, transferred, or retained. 

To protect your privacy, we have adopted the following principles: 

  * Notice 
  * Choice 
  * Security 
  * Access/Accuracy 

## NOTICE

**Information Collection**  
You may access and browse our Website without disclosing any Personal Information. However, if you attempt to use UpClick.com 's services to purchase a product or service online, UpClick.com may request that you voluntarily supply it with Personal Information. UpClick.com uses a secure transmission method for all of its transmissions. UpClick.com receives and stores all information that you enter in our Website and billing pages. In addition, UpClick.com collects information about you during your visit, such as your IP Address and UpClick.com employs its software in order to ascertain your physical location when making a purchase. Except as set forth below, UpClick.com does not collect information from sources such as public records, or private organizations. However, UpClick.com does collect personal information you submit to its clients in order to complete transactions. You are required to provide UpClick.com and its clients with accurate and up-to-date information, and your failure to accurately provide such information could result in the voiding of your agreement(s) with UpClick.com . 

**Information Use**  
UpClick.com is the sole owner of the information collected on its Website. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to Third Parties, except as set forth in this Privacy Policy. UpClick.com shall release data when required by law, to enforce its agreement(s) with you, or to enforce the contract rights of its clients. 

**Information Sharing**   
We ensure that your Personal Information will not be disclosed to anyone other than a government institution or authority when required by law or other regulation, UpClick.com 's affiliated Merchant Bank and card processors as required to process transactions on a credit card, and website owners/operators from which you are purchasing goods and services using UpClick.com ("Third Parties").   

## CHOICE

You may choose whether or not to provide Personal Information to UpClick.com . If you choose not to provide the Personal Information we request, you can still visit most of UpClick.com 's Website, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers, and services that involve our interaction with you. If you chose to have a relationship with UpClick.com , such as a contractual or other business relationship or partnership, you will be required to provide Personal Information in connection with such relationship.   

## SECURITY

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the Personal Information that we have under our control from unauthorized access; improper use or disclosure; unauthorized modification; unlawful destruction or accidental loss. UpClick.com utilizes Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software when receiving and transmitting electronic payments. UpClick.com encrypts the sensitive information that you provide. UpClick.com reveals your credit card number when communicating on a private dedicated line of communication with our associated financial institution.   
In addition, UpClick.com protects your Personal Information off-line. All your information is restricted to our office. Security cards are used to enter our facility. All employees and data processors, who have access to and are associated with the processing of Personal Information, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' Personal Information. UpClick.com conducts background and credit checks on all of its employees prior to employment. UpClick.com employs a User ID and password scheme in order to limit and achieve access to our computer network by our employees and Third Parties.   

## ACCESS/ACCURACY

**Access**   
You may inquire about your Personal Information being held by UpClick.com by contacting us here. Within a week, UpClick.com shall provide you with a copy of the Personal Information that it keeps about you. UpClick.com charges a $25 processing fee for the request. Prior to completing your request, UpClick.com will require that you provide us with proof of your identity. UpClick.com reserves the right to refuse any request for information, though it will communicate the reason for its decision. 

**Accuracy**  
To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, UpClick.com wishes to maintain accurate Personal Information. Where we collect Personal Information from you on our Website, our goal is to provide a means of contacting us should you need to update or correct that Personal Information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible, you may send updates and corrections about your Personal Information by contacting us and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in your Personal Information that we hold as soon as practicable.   

## COOKIES

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the visitor's hard drive containing information about the visitor that can only be read by the server that placed cookie onto the visitor's hard drive. 

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can set your browser to block cookies entirely, delete cookies when you leave the website, notify you when you receive a cookie giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it, or limit the subsequent retrieval of cookies by the website. In addition, there are number of privacy-enhancing tools and software that you may purchase that will enable you to identify and block cookies on a selective basis. Please note that for some websites that require an authorization, cookies are not optional. Users choosing not to accept cookies will probably not be able to access those websites. 

UpClick.com does not employ "cookie" technology on any of its websites.   

## THIRD PARTIES

Occasionally, UpClick.com receives information from Third Parties to compare it to information that you had provided to UpClick.com for fraud prevention purposes.   
Any websites displayed to you by our Website as Internet search results or linked to Internet search results pages provided to you by our Website, including websites owned or operated by our clients, have been developed by Third Parties over which UpClick.com exercises no control. Such websites may send their own cookies to end-users, collect data, or solicit Personal Information from you. UpClick.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites, including such websites' use of any information collected when you are directed to or click through to such websites. Even though such information might not identify you personally, we strongly encourage you to become familiar with the privacy practices of those websites.   

## CHILDREN

UpClick.com does not request, or knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. UpClick.com takes specific steps to protect the privacy of children by making reasonable efforts to ensure that a parent has authorized the collection and/or distribution to Third Parties of the child's Personal Information. Additionally, to ensure that children's privacy is respected on our Website, UpClick.com requires age verification on every inquiry. Furthermore, UpClick.com does not give children the ability to post messages or otherwise distribute information about themselves on our Website.   

## POLICY CHANGES

UpClick.com will make reasonable efforts to maintain an up to date and effective online privacy standards and policy. Whenever UpClick.com makes changes to this policy we will post a notice of this change at the top of the page at [www.UpClick.com](http://www.upclick.com/).

## EFFECTIVE DATE 

This privacy policy is effective immediately. 

## COMMITMENT

We are committed to privacy and are actively involved in and support current industry initiatives to preserve individual privacy rights on the Internet. Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and UpClick.com 's Website is constantly evolving to meet these demands.   
If you have any comments or questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please do not hesitate to contact us.

**While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as possible.**

back to top
